The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
There's nothing good in the recent auctions.
It's disappointing.
Bear with it,
the 4 major sects have been looking for treasures recently.
We'd be lucky if there were any left.
What are they trying to...
I heard that
they are going to the Celestial Realm.
I used almost all of my artifacts
in the war against Xue Yue.
Many sects are looking forward
to the opening of the Celestial Realm.
I have to be fully prepared.
The first step
is to refine another Restriction Flag.
This is...
Do you want this ?
It can improve my Spirit Beast's cultivation ?
Wait here,
I'm going to the Land of the Ancient God.
As long as I don't enter the Ancient God trials,
Tuo Sen shouldn't notice that I am here.
Even if he does,
with my current cultivation,
I should be able to leave this place.
I refined a flag in the Sea of Devils before
but it triggered a tribulation and I was injured.
The Land of the Ancient God
is a realm of its own
so the tribulation shouldn't be able to fall.
This is the last one.
If my is guess wrong
and the tribulation falls now,
it will be hard to protect the flag.
But if I stop now,
the flag won't reach the first stage and will lack strength.
It will hardly help me in the Celestial Realm.
I will gamble !
I won the gamble.
I don't need to worry about tribulations in the Land of the Ancient God.
Let's keep adding restrictions,
maybe I can hit the second stage.
When it does,
its power will be doubled.
Note: Wang Lin refined non-specialized restriction flags before.
Now that he knows more restrictions, he is refining a pure attack restriction flag.
3 days later
With my cultivation,
the second stage is still a step away.
It's okay,
the next tribulation the flag will cause
will be able to save me in a life or death situation.
Note: This scene was originally cut from episode 35, at that time the Blood Sea Warriors give Wang Lin their artifacts to guarantee his safety
This artifact is called the Huan Yuan Beast Trap.
Any beast in the world can be controlled by it for a short time.
In theory, you just need to have enough spiritual energy.
The stronger the beast is,
the more it will consume spiritual energy.
Use it wisely.
It would be great to capture
another beast with this.
Even if I fail,
I can always just leave.
Why is the spiritual energy so thin here ?
Desolate beasts !
Wow, 2 Desolate Beasts are fighting.
Wrong, this toad isn't a Desolate Beast.
It's only a high quality Spirit Beast.
It's still able to fight back,
it must be special.
This Flood Dragon is powerful !
Master, let's capture it.
With my current cultivation,
I can't subdue Desolate Beasts.
But a high quality Spirit Beast is worth a shot.
But can I escape this Flood Dragon ?
It's gonna be tight.
If you don't want to die, don't struggle !
Master,
are you okay ?
This toad is really powerful.
The moment it was captured,
almost all my spiritual energy was absorbed by it.
So this beast is a Thunder Toad.
The beast trap
will regularly absob spiritual energy from my body.
to maintain control of the Thunder Toad.
From now on, I need to prepare in advance
because if this happens during a fight,
it can be very dangerous.
Why are they fighting ?
Enough !
I need to catch my breath,
I can't make mistakes.
6 days later
It's been 6 days !
Aren't you guys done already !?
It's over...
Master, wake up.
There's a big one coming.
With my cultivation, I'm afraid I can't stop this one.
Where are we going next ?
The Foreign Battlefield.
Today, the Foreign Battlefield opens once again.
I hope the elites of the country of Wuwen can seize this opportunity
to raise their cultivations !
Thank you, Lord Envoy.
Sun Wen
Gong Sun country's Envoy
Late stage Nacent Soul
This...
This is...
Why are there so many wandering souls ?!
Is the Foreign Battlefield collapsing ?
What's going on ?!
Someone's in there ?
How did he get in ?
I'm afraid that this fellow cultivator is in a pinch.
Junior Sun Wen,
greets Senior.
Greetings Senior.
Where am I ?
Senior,
this is the country of country Wuwen.
How can such a person be here ?
I feel like I just met my sect's Ancestor.
That was scary !
I have a Restriction Flag, a Thunder Toad,
wandering souls and ancient artifacts ready.
Even the 3 swords sheaths
are being refined by my Origin Soul.
Now,
one last step...
1 year later
Alright.
The past year,
the sword sheaths have been refined one by one.
The artifacts I got from the Blood Sea Warriors
are finally under my control.
But I still can't completely open this scroll
that I got in the Sea of Devils.
Note: This is the scroll I was talking about in the note of episode 24
The day
has finally come.
It's finally starting.
Little friend,
make a good use of the straw hat I lent you.
Otherwise, I'm afraid you won't make it.
Grandpa,
can you continue the story ?
Yes, Grandpa, please continue.
Sure, sure.
It's said that an accident many years ago
caused the death of all the ancient Celestials.
The Celestial Realm was shattered into fragments.
But the cultivators didn't give up.
When the gates of the Celestial Realm open again,
those who obtained a Rain Cauldron will rush in
to look for its remaining treasures.
Falling from the night sky and melting into dust
like water without a source.
Like the difference between clouds and mud,
the truth cannot be found in conflict.
Life and death
are like the moment when the rain falls
and like many other unseparable things.
In this lifetime,
to cultivate the truth, cultivate the world first.
Old grudges had to be settled
because half an inch is engraved into my tree rings.
Use the most vivid love and hate
to ask questions to your fate.
Let your eyes be filled enough with rage
to pierce the heart and the soul
then soften because of the mortals' fireworks.
Only when you bend down can you understand
the hidden edge of the blade.
The human mind is nature,
the rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,
there are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart
to depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.
After struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.
Everywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined
by this endless world.
The human mind is nature,
the rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,
there are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart
to depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.
After struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.
Everywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined
by this endless world.
Snow falls as my hair turns white, winter withers
while prosperity sprouts in summer.
I step into the world, with light at my fingertips,
the law of cause and effect.
I observe the vastness of heaven and earth so I can get rid of evil.
Obsession arises from one thought, life and death arise from one thought.
Reincarnation is not to be feared.